In Tirmidhi, an en-nameel in Islam, which is like Allah with the prayer of Ashkas Yunus, there is no Marum.
En Tirmidhi, un nombre en el Islam, que es como Alá con la oración de Ashkas Yunus, no hay Marum.
Lai Allah Allam Tsubhana's M. is a newborn in Marwarts
M. de Lai Allah Allam Tsubhana es un recién nacido en Marwarts
There is only knowledge of ki
Sólo hay conocimiento de ki.
This is Sigi Dulstikhfar
Este es Sigi Dulstikhfar.
In this world, I have gone to sing in front of my Lord in a simple way.
En este mundo he ido a cantar delante de mi Señor de una manera sencilla.
Lai Allah symbol
Símbolo de Lai Allah
There is no time to fear Allah
No hay tiempo para temer a Allah
Glory be to you
Gloria a ti
So he will not make a mistake
Para que no se equivoque
Kani Kalti Marud
Kani Kalti Marud
I will make mistakes, I am human
Cometeré errores, soy humano.
So just weave it
Así que solo tejelo
O Allah, he did such a thing
Oh Allah, él hizo tal cosa
A shaks on whom is the share of Allah that the Surahs came in Safaat
A shaks sobre quién es la parte de Allah que las Surahs vinieron en Safaat
That if Yunus had not called us in the belly of the stomach with woolen wool, he would have come out on the day when the dead come out of their graves.
Que si Yunus no nos hubiera llamado en el vientre del estómago con lana, habría salido el día en que los muertos salgan de sus tumbas.
Those of them
esos de ellos
In this case, it is such a hot time
En este caso, es un momento tan caluroso.